Phone: (+420) 724 735 822

Email: martin.kozeny@gmail.com

Personal

Born on December 21, 1986.

Czech Republic Citizen.

Marital status: single.

Driving licence: yes (B).

Spoken languages: Czech - mothertongue, English - fluent, German - good, French - basic.

Profile

I have quite a lot experiences with programming in Java (both J2SE and J2EE) and also interested in other programming languages and using alternative programming techniques. I passed during my studies many courses related to artifical intelligence which is also object of my interest. In my current work I deal with J2EE technologies and databases.

Education

Ing. Computer science - software engineering, Czech Technical University in Prague, 2009–2012.

International exchange student of computer science, University of New Orleans, 2011.

CISCO Networks certificate, CCNAE 1, 2010.

Bc. Computer science, Czech Technical University in Prague, 2006–2009.

First Certificate in English (FCE), 2006.

Grammar school Dašická Pardubice, 1998–2006.

Employment

Software developer at Ample cz s.r.o. 2007–present.

Duties: Working on enteprise applications for government and for private sector involving its designing, modeling and implementation. Experiences with databases including data gathering and data normalizing for datawarehouse.

Tourist guide at Kinský dal Borgo, a.s. 2004–2011.

Duties: Tourist guide at castle Kost in summer season.

Databases

Administration

Areas of expertise

Programming languages

Java (J2SE, J2EE) SQL language C/C++ MS SQL Server

Smalltalk MS SQL Server Analysis

Ruby Mondrian

Lisp PostgreSQL Server

Prolog Oracle and also its PL/SQL extension

Haskell MySQL

Tools

Eclipse Administration of Gnu/Linux

NetBeans MS Windows

Ant

ETL graphs Application server Tomcat

Visual Studio JBoss

Enterprise Architect, Astah Apache

CVS, SVN, Git

Web Development

JBoss Seam framework Hibernate Jakarta Struts

Ajax UML 2.0 PHP

CSS Web Services

HTML Testing

XHTML Javascript DocBook

XML JQuery

Realized projects

1: eGORDION

Project	eGORDION (dataGORDION3, nabidkaGORDION, metodikaGORDION,
,	eaukceGORDION)
Position	J2EE developer and system designer
Customer	Public institutions (Minstry of Transport, Ministry of Justice, Ministry of Agricul-
	ture, Ministry of Industry and Trade, Ministry of Education, Czech Post, Faculty
	Hospital Motol, Hospital Na Homolce, VZP, Czech Railways, City of Budejovice,
	City of Pilsen, South Bohemian Region,) and private institutions (Gordion s.r.o.,
	eCentre a.s.,)
Term	2007–2012
Project decription	Design and implementation of modular system for administration of public con-
	tracts - integrated web applications, electronic tool - the auction, electronic submis-
	sion of tenders, the DNS - the dynamic purchasing, www.egordion.cz
Technology	J2EE, JBoss Seam framework 2.0.1., LDAP, Lucene, WebDav, streaming JBoss web-
	services, electronic receipt of tenders, encryption, certificates, applets, Linux / MS
	Windows servers, Postgre SQL, MS SQL Server 2000/2005
Responsibility	Design, development, implementation of specific branch with new features for
	Czech Railways and consultation, service, support

2: Insolvency Register

Project	Insolvency Register
Position	J2EE developer
Customer	Electrolux CZ
Term	6/2009
Project decription	Monitoring insolvency of Electrolux's customers
Technology	J2EE, JBoss Seam framework 2.0.1., Postgre SQL
Responsibility	Design, development

3: Datawarehouse

Project	Datawarehouse
Position	Designer and developer of datawarehouse including ETL processes and web appli-
	cation for the customer
Customer	Electrolux A
Term	1/2009-6/2009
Project decription	Implementation of system providing information for business decisions
Technology	Jakarta Struts, MS SQL Server Analysis, ETL graph plugin for Eclipse
Responsibility	Design and implementation of ETL processes, Datawarehouse cubes and web ap-
	plication enabling operations like slicing etc.

4: Lavamax

Project	Lavamax
Position	J2EE developer and system designer
Customer	Lavamax s.r.o.
Term	6/2009–10/2009
Project decription	ERP system for authorized service company of Electrolux appliances - service order
	management, technician planning, ordering of products, billing, invoicing.
Technology	J2EE, JBoss Seam framework 2.1.2, MS SQL Server 2005
Responsibility	Design and implementation of particular processes (invoicing, ordering, billing, do-
	cuments generating), design and implementation of upselling using webservices
	and persistent queue, support

5: Reklamace

Project	Reklamace
Position	J2EE developer
Customer	Electrolux CZ
Term	4/2010-5/2010
Project decription	Web application providing inserting warranty claims for customers and its admi-
	nistration on Electrolux's side, , www.elux4u.net/reklamace
Technology	J2EE, JBoss Seam framework 2.1.2, MS SQL Server 2000
Responsibility	Implementation of particular processes (life cycle of warranty claim, generating
	documents)

6: dataGORDION3 migration

Project	dataGORDION3 migration
Position	Data transformation process developer
Customer	City of Olomouc, City of Budejovice, Mero,
Term	2009–2010
Project decription	Transform data from relational database dataGORDION2 to relational database da-
	taGORDION3
Technology	ETL graph Eclipse plugin, MS SQL Server 2000/2005
Responsibility	Design and implementation of phases of transformation data from relational da-
	tabase of application dataGORDION2 to relational database of application data-
	GORDION3 using ETL graph Eclipse plugin while preserving all the relational
	dependencies

7: Customer Database

Project	Customer Database
Position	J2EE developer and system designer
Customer	Electrolux CZ
Term	4/2010-5/2010
Project decription	CRM web application for traders with functionalities like planning meetings, at-
	tendance reporting, information on the sale of the products, integration with other
	applications
Technology	J2EE, JBoss Seam framework 2.1.2, MS SQL Server 2000
Responsibility	Implementation of communication between application Reklamace and Customer
	Database using webservices, administration of customers, computing and genera-
	ting output of attendance and appointments, support

8: eTržiště

Project	eTržiště
Position	J2EE developer
Customer	Ministry of Regional Development
Term	9/2011–?
Project decription	Implementation of application according to project documentation of Ministry of
	Regional Development enabling administration of public tenders in a set of pro-
	curement procedures under the Public Procurement Act and outside its range,
	www.tendermarket.cz
Technology	J2EE, JBoss Seam framework 2.2.2, Postgre SQL
Responsibility	Implementation of particular subprocesses (e.g. Cancelation of procurement), com-
	munication with ISVZ using webservices